it is late Summer and the faintest hint
of something crisp is in the air Autumn
is only a whisper but soon enough my
Valley will be transformed into shades
of gold and red and Rich umber I started
this channel in the spring and I think
it only fitting to step away in the fall
[Music]
having a child is an enormous
opportunity for transformation and
growth as is any great change in your
life of that I am certain if you're open
to surrender your ego to let go of the
past in order to welcome a new future
you will lose things along the way it
will not be easy but you may very well
become the person you were meant to be
you may discover peace is no longer
something you're searching for but what
you commit yourself to each day
[Music]
I've been blessed with a little soul and
he has made me realize that I'm not
capable of as much in regards to my work
at this time for years I was in a habit
of overfilling my plate and taking on
more than I could without constant
stress I realize I do need to keep a
balance because it's not just about me
anymore and that is a huge
responsibility and also a gift it is the
beginning of a new Journey a new chapter
a new part of my story and it will take
enormous focus and
mindfulness this experience of creating
short films of finding Beauty in the
mundane celebrating nature and
experimenting with foraging and crafts
all while sharing and connecting with
you has changed my life and challenged
me in the best way all these flowers
things to on your feet
[Music]
over the last couple years I've learned
to be quietly content to nurture a
subtle peace that has grown in my soul
and encompassed my whole self it is the
state of being I will continue to
explore and share with the fairy child
that is now in my life
[Music]
with that being said I've had to come to
the Bittersweet decision to slow down
and downsize that means I will no longer
be regularly uploading I will hold on to
a hope that perhaps I can put up a
little update once a season but honestly
I'm not sure what the future holds I
think I need to close this door in order
to open myself to new possibilities and
so I'm trying not to make plans maybe
when baby is older I will have things a
little more figured out but I'm trying
to be humble and accept that right now I
[Music]
don't I will not be disappearing
completely as I will continue to be
active on patreon where I post monthly
video updates do live streams and host a
casual book club it will soon be home to
my new audiobook as well I'm currently
recording my fiction story the woods and
wisp that will be posted on that
platform next month I've been enjoying a
small and sweet Community where I found
many Kindred Spirits
[Music]
I am permanently retiring my art pieces
from my Etsy shop as I can no longer
keep up with a iCal store if you're
interested I have a sale going on before
closing so that the last dozen or so
Prince can find a home for those
concerned don't worry I will also keep
sending out
postcards however since I know I will
not see the vast majority of you for the
foreseeable future know that I'm sending
you so much love and many blessings as
you go forward on your own extraordinary
Journey keep shining your light no
matter how dark things seem sometimes
and and it is my greatest hope that at
some point over the last several years
I've brought you some small moment of
Peace take care little fairy goodbye
[Music]